So what we're doing here today is we're
just doing a full walkthrough of the like
how to just really set up quad code, how
to really set up quad and just in general,
like how to use AI in your role, right?
As much as possible.
We'll go through like some mock examples
and overall we'll set us up for success.
To start off with.
Go to Claude and go ahead to chat.
And I would just create a new chat.
I would just say, and what I do is I use
Whisper Flow guys, so I just press the
button on my keyboard with Whisper Flow.
It's a plugin you could use.
CLO also has its own dictation plugin.
I use Whisper Flow on every app though,
so that's why I use a separate one.
And I'm just gonna talk
out the prompts, right?
I'm gonna say, Hey here's
my ideas and thoughts.
I wanna create about a one hour
training video with Audrey.
So keep it simple.
Gimme like a quick checklist and gimme
some examples I can use, especially around
the projects that we can use this for.
But it, so that way we can, give
a true demonstration on how to
reuse like the power of cloud,
cloud code and cloud cowork.
And then whisper flow will
automatically paste it there.
Supposed to at least put that there.
That's my example.
Instructions.
And then whisper flow.
Boom.
So I'll go ahead and complete
this part where I was talking.
Boom.
So this is literally what I just said.
On the recording, and I'll put
here, this is my thought to that.
I note to what I wanna cover.
So you can see that you always wanna use
little things like this that are huge
difference, but not a big difference.
Not a huge difference is
breaking up your prompts.
So that way Claude knows I'm talking
to it here and then that way there's
a delimiter and it knows that
here's the example stuff below.
I still labeled it though,
so it's a not that huge deal.
So go ahead.
I hit send on that.
That's gonna go ahead and
pop back a quick plan for us.
It's a pretty simple task, so
should only take a couple seconds.
Then from there, Audrey, while
we're doing that, as you can see,
it's already given us the, it's
starting to give us a plan there.
Audrey, you're in.
Can you go ahead and I'll stop
share for a sec and if you
can go ahead and share screen.
Let's go ahead and download the cloud
app, and then we're gonna open up
terminal too as well for all the users.
Anybody watching this?
Do you have a Windows
computer or a Mac computer?
I have Windows.
Windows.
Okay.
Most people probably will
that get into this training.
So when you go to Windows and you
already have the app downloaded,
but let's pretend like you don't.
Yes.
Audrey, right?
Okay.
First time we did it, it was
a little bit of a pain, right?
Yeah.
We have, all we have to do is just
open up a tab, just in your browser,
it looks like you're using Chrome.
I just wanna type in claude.ai.
If you don't have an account,
make sure you go to Cloud ai.
I can't tell you how many times people
go to just type in cloud ai and then
whatever search engine they're using,
we will give them a different platform
that uses Claude and then now they're
signing up for something different.
So make sure when you go sign
it up, it looks just like this.
Let's create an account.
Then you go ahead and you'll create
an account and it'll take you to
this page and you'll go ahead and
you'll have an account, right?
And you can sign up for free.
If you do wanna use quad code though,
you do have to be on the Pro plan.
I think it's 25 or $30 per month.
It'd be the best investment
that you make probably this
year, maybe in your entire life.
And that's not an exaggeration.
So just sign up for the Pro account.
You don't have to, Audrey, obviously,
you're on the Pro account already.
But if you're seeing this you can
sign up for free, but you will
be prompted to sign up for a pro
account if you wanna use quad code.
You'll wanna do that.
And if you're seeing this and you're
a virtual assistant your employer will
take care of it and will pay for it.
If you're seeing this in your virtual
assistant and you wanna be proactive
and you can afford to pay for it,
I highly recommend you do you can
start using it right away again.
It'd be well worth it.
And if you're seeing this in your
employer, you want to offer this to you.
You're gonna pay for this, for your
virtual assistant or for your assistant
or whoever, whatever role they're filling.
'Cause this is the superpowers, right?
So let's pretend you just signed up for a
free account or for a pro account, Audrey.
Now what you'll do is you'll
just go to the, yeah, the app.
You got the free account.
First off, we have to
download the app, right?
They haven't downloaded this point.
It'll be on your dashboard
when you log in, right?
When you in cloud.
So go ahead and log into your
account, Audrey, into my real account.
Yeah, go ahead.
Okay, hold on.
Let me the other one.
I'm already logged in.
There you go.
So on the left hand side and the bottom
left, you see that little down arrow
you can see I just hover over it.
Yep.
You can see get apps extensions.
Go ahead and click on it, Audrey.
And that's where once you're
in your account, this is where
you'll actually like download.
So you'll see cowork, you
can download that for Windows
that's gonna download the app.
And then when it does, it'll download,
you go through the download process
and open up the app like you'll see
Audrey has it on her on her desktop.
Now for cloud code, we're gonna go ahead
and install it in the terminal as well.
So go ahead and open that up.
Audrey.
So they can see how to do that real quick.
It's very easy.
I know it's gonna be a little
scary on your computer, Audrey.
Just go ahead and hit search and type CMD.
If you're on a Windows, it's CMD.
If you're on a mat, it's terminal.
And so it's command prompt.
You hit open and then all you
do literally is Audrey Copy.
Just show 'em real quick how
to copy that one piece of code.
Just scroll down a little bit.
No, not cool.
Just scroll down.
No, just scroll down a little bit.
There'll be one line of code
for them to install right there.
Not the Mac window, but for
the Windows Power shell.
Yeah.
Or Windows CMD.
That might actually be more appropriate.
There you go.
So depending on what
Windows computer you're on.
If you have command prompt like
this, then you can just install that.
Really, just click one one piece,
the copy, that one piece of code,
hit enter and it'll install it.
Now, one could be is that if you're on
a Windows, you might have to install gi.
If you haven't already a four, and you
literally just go to right there where
it says Windows requires get for windows.
Just click that link, Audrey,
right below that on your window.
CMD.
On the quad code page.
Yep.
And then you just go here and you
just click on that like X 64 setup
or whatever your computer takes,
and it automatically installs it.
After that, you restart your
computer, you come back to the app.
Let's pretend like we
just did that, Audrey.
So you go back to the app now
you have quad code installed.
Do I have that app on the computer
at this point they have it downloaded
and they've installed quad code.
So go ahead and click
outta that page please.
The command.
That.
Yeah, that's right.
And then now let's go ahead and
focus on the app at this point.
If you're watching this video and
following along, you've already
signed up for a pro account.
You've already downloaded the
app on your computer, and you've
already installed cloud code and
terminal and installed Git on.
If you're on a Windows computer, on Mac,
it probably already has it installed,
so you don't have to worry about that.
But either way, at this point, you've
already restarted your computer.
Audrey, go ahead and pull up the app.
Let's keep that open for
right now as the main window.
The app for the computer on your right.
Yep.
You can go ahead and just make it bigger,
so that way that's all we're seeing.
So now we're at this 0.5
minutes later, right?
You've already, you've got
you everything installed.
Now you're good to go.