So what is it we're looking at?
You have the middle on, in
the middle part up top there.
Audrey, you can see we
have chat, cowork and code.
It's three different areas
in which we can work in.
Chat is, here's my question.
It gives me back an answer.
Cowork is it's cloud code, but for
the rest of the business, if you
open up a new session, there you go.
You can see here, you can, so you can
customize means that you can like,
connect it to all your different
tools like your Google Drive,
your calendar, everything else.
Schedule means you can
schedule tasks to run daily.
For instance, Audrey, I know
you do clickup automatic
tasks every single day, right?
Where it has a automatic
run updates the clickup.
Same thing with like
your calendar and email.
Then don't worry about dispatch.
I'm working on the left hand side,
by the way, guys, where it says new
tasks, search scheduled dispatch.
I just don't worry about dispatch.
It's actually where you can
connect your phone to it.
That's pretty simple.
You guys can figure that out by yourself.
So don't worry about that part.
And like I said, customize where you
can connect all your tools and stuff.
Click on it real quick for them
so they can see it, just so they
can be familiar with that screen.
And they're doing this on their own.
Audrey where where it says ideas
and customize, hit customize.
And boom, you can connect your apps.
Skills is a a way in which you can
extend the abilities of Quad Code
won't cover that in this video.
There's also plugins as well, and
that's where it can get confusing
what to do and when that's a
different video for a different day.
Let's go ahead and go over to where
it says New task again, Audrey.
And then in the middle, let's go
ahead and move over to Quad Code.
So we just covered chat, we covered
cowork and then we have quad code.
This is where the, a lot
of the magic happens.
Majority of the time, you're
gonna use quad code to build
and do the more intense stuff.
Cowork is something you'll use to help
you brainstorm and organize and chat
is something that where can do quick
searches And quick one-off answers.
So the majority of this, the rest of
this video is gonna be in quad code.