So a couple things to notice here.
Actually before we actually
do that, one thing to do is
let's get your settings done.
And Audrey, if you can go to the left
on the bottom, click on your name.
Or the, or that right there.
That's fine.
You did the right thing.
Same thing.
Settings.
Two things that I do, one
thing you definitely want do
is under quad code in settings
on the left hand side where
it says settings on that list.
There's not in the middle of the page
there, Audrey, where it says settings.
Then you see quad code in that list.
It's about five up.
There you go.
You'll want to hit allow
bypass permissions mode
right there in the middle.
You've already got yours turned on Audrey.
But for if you're first time downloading
the app, it's your first time working it.
You'll want to enable that mode.
You don't have to.
If you don't do that, then
what happens when you use it?
It's gonna ask you for
permission to do everything.
So you're gonna be pressing that
allow permissions button like a
hundred times sometimes, and it can
get really unproductive or slow.
Slow with getting stuff done.
So we got that turned on, and then the
other one, Audrey, is Claude in Chrome.
If you can click on that
and then you'll want to go ahead
and make sure that is good to go.
Make sure that's turned on.
Go ahead.
You can click on it, hit allow
extension, and then it's gonna go ahead
and allow, it's gonna, you're giving
it permission to use your browser.
So if it ever needs to log into
something or check something on the
internet, that's what that means.
One other setting depending on
your situation, if you go to usage.
In the setting tab.
There you go.
Here I always turn on extra usage.
Audrey's turn on here, right?
So she's spent an extra $132.
They'll, does that intimidate you?
We do a lot of stuff
with cloud code, right?
You may not use it that much, but there
is a certain amount of usage that comes
with each plan, and sometimes you may
want to go over to finish a project.
I personally turn the that on.
You don't have to.
You definitely want to turn on
the cloud code, enable bypass
permissions and the cloud and chrome.
You wanna have those two turn on?
For sure.
Audra, let's go ahead and
go back to the cloud code.
Just hit new session up top left and
that'll bring you back to cloud code.
So now we're here.
What are we looking at?
First thing is you have this you
have this box in front of you.
Then it says Auto accept
edits and select folder.
And it has your model on the right
hand side, which is on at 4.6.
And it says local.
Don't worry about the model in the local
part on the right hand side, too much.
Just pay attention.
There's that microphone there.
So if you're not using whisper flow,
you'll definitely want to use that
microphone button 'cause you're gonna
wanna talk out your prompts and you'll
see that here shortly when we do that.
In the meantime.
The one thing, two things if keep
in mind is you always want to select
a folder for your project, right?
You're gonna be building something
that's, there's gonna be a
lot of files that are created.
If you're building a, something that's
technical, like a website or an app
or you're launching like some sort of
like agents or scripts or whatever.
There's files that are created
that are associated with that.
If they're scattered all over your
computer, then the app or whatever
it's you're doing, may or may not
work to the level that you want it
to, especially if you're gonna keep
coming back to it over and over.
So go ahead and select that Audrey
and just go ahead and what I do, go
ahead and choose a different folder.
So choose different folder
like, yeah, there you go.
What I always do if you don't have
to do this is go to the desktop
and.
Go to create new folder, right?
If you don't already have a folder for
what you're working on now, if you're
is, this is something you've already been
working on where you have some files, you
wanna create a presentation, or you are,
working on this in a different, platform
or whatever else it is, or a different,
situation, then just select that folder.
But if you don't, then create
a new folder for Audrey.
You just called this training video.
And then now whatever we
create will be in that folder.
Go ahead and say select folder.
So you see that there now
a change to training video.
Keep in mind that whenever you're doing
this in cloud, cowork, cloud code or
any other platform, honestly you wanna
make sure you're working outta the right
folder so that way you don't mess up
stuff or get lost or get unorganized.
Other thing I tend to do more often than
not, and this is a comfort thing, as well
as like just a, the, a workflow preference
is where it says auto accept edits.
Audrey, you click on that and change
it to bypass permissions mode.
It's very rare.
And it depends on what
you're doing here, right?
But it is very rare that it's gonna
ask you to do something that's not
gonna that's gonna be harmful, right?
Most of the time you are gonna want
it to just go do it, and you not
ask you like a million questions
or ask you for permission every
time, for every little thing.
So play with that.
If you're watching this video have it
in accept edits or plan mode and see how
much the permissions and stuff come up.
And also just keep in mind that
depending on your task you may or
may not want to have that enabled.
I'll give you an example where, a
good example, bad example real quick.
'cause that is an important feature.
A good example is if I'm building an app.
For instance, I just built an app for a
go to market, project where it's sending
out cold emails and things like that.
I know what I want with that app, so I
gave it a full long prompt and I told
it bypass permissions and go build it.
Whereas a month ago I was working
on a project and I had this open.
In cursor, which I'll show
you later on this video.
And I told her to clean up the
folder 'cause I had so many files
that we weren't using and it went
through and deleted all the files.
So I then I had to try and figure out
how to, like, how to get that reversed.
And luckily I was able to save.
The main files that I needed.
But it went through and deleted it.
And once I told her to do it, it
was in bypass permissions mode
and it just went and deleted.
I couldn't stop it.
Just be aware of what tasks you're
using it for, but in 90% of the cases,
bypass permissions mode is what I
have it on, because I don't want
to have to give it permission for
everything and have it waiting on me.
All right.
Cool.
So now we've got that out the way.
Let's get to the fun stuff.