A you ready?
Good.
All right.
Cool.
Go ahead.
What we're gonna do is we're gonna build
out I'm gonna show you like how I do these
different, like these different projects,
like how I build out my system, right?
Because I'm always, you wanna look
at it like from a mindset perspective
of, Hey, I'm no longer doing stuff.
I'm now the thinker and
orchestrator, the expert.
And I'm telling my teams of
agents what to do, right?
So I'm gonna have at least three different
tabs open, and depending on what my
project is or what I'm doing for my
role, then I might have three or four
different terminal sessions open too.
And I'm really just bouncing back
and forth answering questions.
And Claude is the one
doing the work from now on.
Okay.
So to do that, let's take a step back.
Azure.
Lemme get the screen share please.
What I'll do is, first, let's go check
up on what Claude said, because we're
gonna follow the instructions today.
So here we are.
Install and setup.
Claude has already, is
already ahead of us, right?
We already did this, install
this up on desktop and notice I
just gave it a permission, right?
I gave it a prompt, and then
I had some thoughts on what
I wanted to do today, right?
Claude built this out
for us already, right?
So now we have a checklist
of what we're doing.
We just did download and install,
and this is not scripted guys, right?
This is how good these models are.
This is how good these tools are.
So use your tools, right?
So we installed cloud and terminal,
we walk through settings, and this
is something I'm gonna do later on.
So our prompting and cloud desktop.
So this is where we're at now.
And then, let's see here,
three live demos, right?
So project one cloud intake
and outreach document, right?
New prospect, Google Review.
Okay.
Brief, and this is actually stuff
that's CLA has very good memory.
So this is all stuff that's
personal to me from past projects.
So
I'm actually gonna correct it
here and just say, Hey, these are
great, these are personal to me.
I need general projects for a training
video for three different roles in
a business, let's say recruiting
operations and for software development.
So I'm correcting it here 'cause I
actually wasn't specific enough in my
prompt what I was looking forward to do.
So it's gonna correct that part.
In the meantime, we've got our
checklist here and it's gonna redo
this and re-put that here in a second.
In the meantime let me go in and let
me just ad-lib this a little bit.
And we'll come back and we'll
check this off as we go.
First thing is showing prompting,
which I actually did with the outward
prompt open multiple Windows desktop.
Okay, cool.
And demonstrate the feedback loop.
Got it.
All right.
So we're gonna do that part and then we'll
actually start job subscription provider.
All right, cool.
This is actually perfect candidate
screening interview question generator.
It's actually given me.
Yeah, so we can do these.
This is actually good.
We can just sit with this, right?
But I'm looking forward to.
All right, so let's go with let's say.
I see what it did.
Okay, cool.
So this is a actual software development.
Lemme be more clear.
So a specific project for that.
I, if I was in a role of
an operations manager.
If I was in the role of a recruiting
or a recruiter for a company,
and then if I was in the role
of a software developer, right?
Three little simple things like software
developer might be a website or app
and a recruiter might be somebody
who is, doing recruiting operations.
So the candidate screener is fine, so
you don't have to worry about that.
Operations manager might be somebody
who's doing Clickup, or some other
project management, just to be clear.
So just gimme those other two.
Recruiting is fine 'cause you gimme an
example here for that and that's fine.
And then if you could always, if you
could actually update the checklist
so that way that's up to date,
that would be awesome too, as well.
So you guys can see it's obviously
not perfect and you're going to get,
the clearer you are the better, right?
So I'm glad that actually
happen on videos.
Who can see that?
That it doesn't always just
come out perfect every time.