So what is it we're looking at?
You have, uh, the middle on, in
the middle part, uh, up top there.
Um, Audrey, you can see we
have chat, cowork and code.
It's three different areas
in which we can work in.
Um, chat is, here's a, here's my question.
It gives me back an answer.
Cowork is kind of like, it's cloud code,
but for the rest of the business, if
you open up a new session, there you go.
Um, you can see here, you can, so
you can, um, customize means that
you can like, connect it to all your
different tools like your Google
Drive, your calendar, everything else.
Um.
Schedule means you can
schedule tasks to run daily.
Uh, for instance, Audrey, I
know you do clickup automatic
tasks every single day, right?
Where it has like a automatic
run updates the clickup.
Same thing with like
your calendar and email.
Um.
Then don't worry about dispatch.
I'm, I'm working on the left hand
side, by the way, guys, where it says
new tasks, search scheduled dispatch.
Um, I just don't worry about dispatch.
It's actually where you can
connect your phone to it.
That's pretty simple.
You guys can figure that out by yourself.
So don't worry about that part.
And like I said, customize where you
can connect all your tools and stuff.
Click on it real quick for them
so they can see it, just so they
can be familiar with that screen.
And they're doing this on their own.
Audrey, where, where, uh, where it says
ideas and customize, hit customize.
And boom, you can connect your apps.
Uh, skills is a, um, a way in
which you can extend the abilities
of Quad Code won't cover that
in this, this, this, um, video.
Uh, there's also plugins as well,
and that's where it can get kind of
confusing what to do and when that's
a different video for a different day.