so I am an operations expert, uh, at
a, b, C, uh, 1, 2, 3 company, and I'm
looking for a, I need you help me with
a. Kind of streamlining my operations.
Right now we're using Clickup.
We have go high level CRM,
and it's all over the place.
I need a home base.
I wanna be able to, to, from just
this one spot, be able to connect
with Clickup, make changes, and have
you help 'em with project management.
I need you to, uh, connect to go
high level CRM, make changes and
help with project management.
I need you to, um, help me
with managing my email account.
It's a Gmail with my
company, Google Workspace.
I need to connect with my calendar and I
have two different calendars on Google,
um, that I'm looking to, uh, connect with.
Uh, but they're both on Google Calendar.
And overall, I want to
be able to have a simple.
Um, like dashboard to kind of work off
here on my local com, my local computer
to where I can, uh, really just kind
of talk to you or use the dashboard
and I can actually just like, you
know, um, kind of make changes, manage
projects, and send out communications,
check my email, everything else right?
So I'm not a developer.
I'm non-technical.
I don't know how this stuff works.
Uh, I only needed to work on my local
computer right now while I'm at work,
and I want to be able to just kind of
check stuff and see, uh, make changes.
So click up.
Go high level CRM and you
could put any CRM here guys,
for anybody's watching this.
Um, same.
Go high is one of the most
popular ones out there.
Um, click up.
Go high level, my email and my calendar.
If you could help me to create a home
base here where I can talk to you and
you can kind of keep me up to date
on stuff, as well as make changes
and help me organize everything,
that would really help out a lot.
Please let me know what you need from me.
Again, I'm non-technical.
I'm not a developer.
I don't know how to do anything,
so please also just do it
for me please too, as well.