It said, great news.
I, and I already have these installed.
So for me it's a little
bit, uh, different, right?
But for you it would say, all right, cool.
Here, here's how to connect,
click up, here's how to connect,
go to calendar and Gmail, right?
Um, go high level.
There's no prebuilt connector,
but, and look at this guys.
It actually went and found it, right?
You can gimme your access key.
Um, one thing to note here is that, um.
There's three things, three things
that you wanna always ask about, right?
Because it, it actually, it can do it
through API key, but I personally know
there's also what's called an MCP.
Right?
And so I'll show you
this by typing it out.
And also I'm teaching whoever
who is watching this video.
There's cps, there's skills, and um,
there's a, something called CLI, right?
You don't have to know what they are
to know that you want those, right?
There's also something called, um.
Uh, plugins, but those are gonna
be transitioned out, so I'm not
gonna teach that too much here.
'cause by the time you watch this
video, it may not even be relevant.
Right.
Um,
so thank you for that.
Uh, what about, uh, I heard about,
there's something called like A MCP.
Uh, what is that?
And is there one of those available
for like, go high level or Clickup?
And then I also heard about skills.